A Guide to the International Education Board records FA062
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1920-1960; 1
  - Fellowships in Science, 3
    - Herman Fink, 1925-1928 (Box 48, Folder 724)
    - Vladimir Fock, 1926-1928 (Box 48, Folder 725)
    - Charles Focken, 1926-1927 (Box 48, Folder 726)
    - Lester Ford, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 727)
    - Adriance Foster, 1926-1930 (Box 48, Folder 728)
    - John S. Foster, 1926-1936 (Box 48, Folder 729)
    - R. H. Fowler, 1924-1937 (Box 48, Folder 730)
    - Bjorn Forn, 1925-1928 (Box 49, Folder 731)
    - Goltfried Frankel, 1925-1927 (Box 49, Folder 732)
    - Jacob Frenkel, 1925-1926 (Box 49, Folder 733)
      Electrodynamics.
    - Rudolf Frericks, 1928-1930 (Box 49, Folder 734)
    - Herbert Friedman, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 735)
    - Paul Frohlich, 1924-1933 (Box 49, Folder 736)
    - Frederick Frost, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 737)
    - Alexander Frum, 1925-1926 (Box 49, Folder 738)
    - Erwin Frues, 1925-1929 (Box 49, Folder 739)
    - Eugen Gabritschevsky, 1924-1930 (Box 49, Folder 740)
    - Georg Gamow, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 741)
    - Milam Garrett, 1924-1926 (Box 49, Folder 742)
    - Ramon Gaviola, 1927-1929 (Box 49, Folder 743)
    - E. Gebauer-Fulnegg, 1926-1932 (Box 49, Folder 744)
    - Max Geiger, 1928 (Box 49, Folder 745)
    - Louis Genevois, 1926-1928 (Box 49, Folder 746)
      Physiological chemistry.
    - Harold Geppert, 1927-1931 (Box 49, Folder 747)
    - John Gergen, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 748)
    - Ferdinando Gimesi, 1924-1928 (Box 49, Folder 749)
      Hydrobiology.
    - Raymond Girton, 1926-1928 (Box 49, Folder 750)
    - Alexander Goetz, 1926-1934 (Box 49, Folder 751)
    - Sydney Goldstein, 1927-1928 (Box 49, Folder 752)
    - Wassily Gontcharoff, 1925-1934 (Box 49, Folder 753)
    - Walter Gordon, 1924-1925 (Box 49, Folder 754)
    - Hans Gottlieb Billroth, 1924-1927 (Box 50, Folder 755)
    - Samuel Goudsmit, 1926-1928 (Box 50, Folder 756)
    - Karl Grandjot, 1928-1931 (Box 50, Folder 757)
    - Gilbert Greenwood, 1925-1932 (Box 50, Folder 758)
    - Zygmont Grodzinski, 1925-1929 (Box 50, Folder 759)
    - Stephen Grynaeus, 1924-1928 (Box 50, Folder 760)
    - Frank T. Gucker, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 761)
    - Raymond Guerard des Lauriers, 1925-1931 (Box 50, Folder 762)
    - Jonas Gullberg, 1925-1928 (Box 50, Folder 763)
      Anatomy.
    - Ronald Gurney, 1926-1931 (Box 50, Folder 764)
      Atomic physics.
    - Arthur Haas, 1925-1926 (Box 50, Folder 765)
    - Otto Halpern, 1928-1930 (Box 50, Folder 766)
    - Joseph A. Harris, 1926-1933 (Box 50, Folder 767)
    - Louis Harris, 1925-1937 (Box 50, Folder 768)
    - Douglas Hartree, 1928 (Box 50, Folder 769)
    - Anna M. Hartsema, 1925-1931 (Box 50, Folder 770)
    - Rudolph Hasche, 1925-1926 (Box 50, Folder 771)
    - Helmuth Hasse, 1925 (Box 50, Folder 772)
    - Odd Hassell, 1924-1926 (Box 50, Folder 773)
    - Torsten Hasselstrom, 1926-1930 (Box 50, Folder 774)
    - Frederick Hayes, 1928-1933 (Box 50, Folder 775)
    - Selig Hecht, 1924-1927 (Box 50, Folder 776)
    - Anatol Heintz, 1929-1931 (Box 50, Folder 777)
      Paleontology.
    - Werner Heisenberg, 1924-1929 (Box 50, Folder 778)
      Astrophysics.
    - Walter Heitler, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 779)
    - P. Herasymenko, 1928 (Box 50, Folder 780)
    - Enrich Herlinger, 1924-1928 (Box 51, Folder 782)
      Mineralogy.
    - Melville Herskovits, 1924-1929 (Box 51, Folder 783)
      Anthropology and psychology.
    - Alfred Hetlich, 1927-1930 (Box 51, Folder 784)
    - Jaroslav Heyrovsky, 1926-1938 (Box 51, Folder 785)
    - Hope Hibbard, 1927-1936 (Box 51, Folder 786)
    - James Hibben, 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 787)
      Photochemistry.
    - Einar Hille, 1925-1928 (Box 51, Folder 788)
    - Stanislaus Hiller, 1925-1934 (Box 51, Folder 789)
    - Max Hirmer, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 790)
    - G. C. Hirsch, 1924-1929 (Box 51, Folder 791)
    - J. W. Hladky, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 792)
    - Vaclav Hlavaty, 1927-1931 (Box 51, Folder 793)
    - Leigh Hoadley, 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 794)
    - Dorothy Hoffert, 1923-1925 (Box 51, Folder 795)
    - Alexander Hoffman, 1925-1934 (Box 51, Folder 796)
    - Karl Hofler, 1928-1929 (Box 51, Folder 797)
    - T. R. Hogness, 1925-1927 (Box 51, Folder 798)
    - Henry F. Holden, 1924 (Box 51, Folder 799)
    - Helmut Holn, 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 800)
    - Heinz Hopf, 1926-1934 (Box 51, Folder 801)
    - Karl Horovitz, 1924-1938 (Box 51, Folder 802)
    - Hobart J. Hoskins, 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 803)
      Paleobotany.
    - Sherill Houghton, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 804)
    - Erich Huckel, 1926-1933 (Box 52, Folder 805)
    - Leon Hufnagel, 1927-1929 (Box 52, Folder 806)
    - Erik Hulthen, 1925-1927 (Box 52, Folder 807)
    - Frederick Hund, 1925-1935 (Box 52, Folder 808)
    - Witwold Hurewicz, 1926-1934 (Box 52, Folder 809)
    - C. R. Hursch, 1924-1925 (Box 52, Folder 810)
    - George E. Hutchinson, 1925-1926 (Box 52, Folder 811)
    - E. A. Hylleraas, 1926-1928 (Box 52, Folder 812)
    - Laurence Irving, 1925-1937 (Box 52, Folder 813)
    - Dimiter Ivanov, 1926-1927 (Box 52, Folder 814)
    - Werner Jacobs, 1924-1927 (Box 52, Folder 815)
    - Vojtech Jarnik, 1927-1929 (Box 52, Folder 816)
    - M. Jerewski, 1924-1929 (Box 52, Folder 817)
    - A. Joffe, 1925-1926 (Box 52, Folder 818)
    - Pascaul Jordan, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 819)
    - Wiladijslaw Kapuscinski, 1927-1934 (Box 52, Folder 820)
    - Jovan Karamata, 1929-1934 (Box 52, Folder 821)
    - A. Karssen, 1925-1931 (Box 52, Folder 822)
    - Bila Kerekjarto, 1924-1925 (Box 52, Folder 823)
    - Cecil V. King, 1923-1925 (Box 52, Folder 824)
    - Albert Kirrmann, 1928 (Box 52, Folder 825)
    - George Kistiakowsky, 1925-1928 (Box 52, Folder 826)
    - Hendril Kloosterman, 1927-1932 (Box 53, Folder 827)
    - Helmuth Kneser, 1924-1932 (Box 53, Folder 828)
    - Paul N. Kogerman, 1926-1928 (Box 53, Folder 829)
    - Vladimir Korinek, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 830)
    - H. Koschmieder, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 831)
    - Anthony Kozlowski, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 832)
    - Frances Krbek, 1925-1930 (Box 53, Folder 833)
    - Niclas Kritikos, 1923-1931 (Box 53, Folder 834)
    - Peter Kruger, 1928-1936 (Box 53, Folder 835)
    - George Krutkow, 1924-1933 (Box 53, Folder 836)
    - Walter Kuhn, 1924-1926 (Box 53, Folder 837)
    - Alfons Kunz, 1924-1926 (Box 53, Folder 838)
    - Ralph De Laer Kronig, 1927-1928 (Box 53, Folder 839)
    - Rene Lagrange, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 840)
    - Rudolph Langer, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 841)
    - Carney Landis, 1925-1926 (Box 53, Folder 842)
    - Wolfgang Langenbeck, 1925-1935 (Box 53, Folder 843)
    - Alex Langseth Jensen, 1928-1929 (Box 53, Folder 844)
    - Otto Laporte, 1924-1933 (Box 53, Folder 845)
    - Charles Lassovozky, 1924-1938 (Box 53, Folder 846)
    - Boris Lawrentjen, 1925-1926 (Box 53, Folder 847)
      Histology.
    - F. E. Lehmann, 1925-1927 (Box 53, Folder 848)
    - Julius F. Lehmann, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 849)
    - Sam Lenher, 1926-1929 (Box 53, Folder 850)
    - Jahn Lennard-Jones, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 851)
    - Harry Levy, 1925-1931 (Box 53, Folder 852)
    - Bernard Lewis, 1926-1928 (Box 53, Folder 853)
    - Hans Lewy, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 854)
    - Alex E. Lindh, 1926-1932 (Box 54, Folder 855)
    - Mayme Logsdon, 1924-1930 (Box 54, Folder 856)
    - Fritz W. London, 1926-1928 (Box 54, Folder 857)
    - Egon Lorenz, 1925-1934 (Box 54, Folder 858)
      Biophysics.
    - Renke G. Lubben, 1926-1927 (Box 54, Folder 859)
    - Hakon Lund, 1924-1926 (Box 54, Folder 860)
    - Eli Lurie, 1927-1928 (Box 54, Folder 861)
    - Nicolas Lusin, 1926-1927 (Box 54, Folder 862)
    - Elizabeth McCoy, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 863)
      Bacteriology.
    - Felix Machatschki, 1927-1929 (Box 54, Folder 864)
    - Michel Macheboeuf, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 865)
      Biological chemistry.
    - Wilhelm Maier, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 866)
    - Felix Mainx, 1927-1928 (Box 54, Folder 867)
    - Branimir Males, 1927-1936 (Box 54, Folder 868)
    - S. Mandelbrojt, 1924-1931 (Box 54, Folder 869)
    - Erich Manegold, 1925-1946 (Box 54, Folder 870)
    - Charles Manneback, 1927-1930 (Box 54, Folder 871)
    - Alfred J. Maria, 1926-1927 (Box 54, Folder 872)
    - Wilhelm Marinelli, 1924-1927 (Box 54, Folder 873)
    - Neda Marinesco, 1927 (Box 54, Folder 874)
    - Josef Mattauch, 1925-1929 (Box 54, Folder 875)
    - Herbert Mayer, 1927-1928 (Box 54, Folder 876)
    - Joseph Mayer, 1928-1930 (Box 54, Folder 877)
    - Karl Mayrhofer, 1927-1934 (Box 54, Folder 878)
    - Robert Mazet, 1926-1932 (Box 54, Folder 879)
    - Karl Meissner, 1924-1926 (Box 55, Folder 880)
    - Demetrius Menchoff, 1926-1934 (Box 55, Folder 881)
    - Karl Menger, 1925-1934 (Box 55, Folder 882)
    - Gaylord Merrimen, 1926-1927 (Box 55, Folder 883)
    - Anton Meyer, 1927-1928 (Box 55, Folder 884)
    - Karl Meyer, 1927-1929 (Box 55, Folder 885)
    - Arthur Mills, 1929-1931 (Box 55, Folder 886)
    - Peter Milovidov, 1927-1928 (Box 55, Folder 887)
      Cytology.
    - Voukitch Mitchovitch, 1925 (Box 55, Folder 888)
    - Max Morand, 1925-1933 (Box 55, Folder 889)
    - Friedrich Moser, 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 890)
    - Alexander Muralt, 1928 (Box 55, Folder 891)
    - Trygve Najell, 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 892)
    - D. N. Nassonov, 1925-1926 (Box 55, Folder 893)
    - Ludwig Neder, 1924-1926 (Box 55, Folder 894)
    - Alexander Neukomm, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 895)
    - John L. von Neumann, 1926-1938 (Box 55, Folder 896)
    - Rolf Nevalinna, 1928-1934 (Box 55, Folder 897)
    - Maxwell Newman, 1928-1929 (Box 55, Folder 898)
    - George Neyman, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 899)
    - James B. Nickols, 1925-1932 (Box 55, Folder 900)
    - Karl Niessen, 1925-1932 (Box 55, Folder 901)
    - Lathar W. Nordheim, 1927-1928 (Box 55, Folder 902)
    - Erich Nuerbergk, 1928 (Box 55, Folder 903)
    - Wikter Oberguggenberger, 1927 (Box 55, Folder 904)
    - Ivar Oftedal, 1929-1931 (Box 55, Folder 905)
      Physical crystalography.
    - Otto Oldenberg, 1924-1926 (Box 56, Folder 906)
    - Oystein Ore, 1924-1927 (Box 56, Folder 907)
    - Boris Orelkin, 1924-1929 (Box 56, Folder 908)
    - A. Ostrowski, 1929-1934 (Box 56, Folder 909)
    - Eugen Pascu, 1928-1938 (Box 56, Folder 910)
    - A. Pannekock, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 911)
    - Alan Parker, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 912)
    - Raymond Parker, 1927-1929 (Box 56, Folder 913)
    - Pasquale Pasquini, 1926-1928 (Box 56, Folder 914)
    - Vjacheslav Pavlov, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 915)
    - Vladimir Pavlov, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 916)
    - Tadija Pejovic, 1924-1930 (Box 56, Folder 917)
    - Echo Pepper, 1925-1926 (Box 56, Folder 918)
    - Nicolas Perrakis, 1926-1936 (Box 56, Folder 919)
    - Enrico Persico, 1925-1933 (Box 56, Folder 920)
    - Hans Petersson, 1926-1932 (Box 56, Folder 921)
    - Jarmila Petrova, 1926-1927 (Box 56, Folder 922)
    - Hans Petterson, 1925-1928 (Box 56, Folder 923)
    - Sydney Pike, 1927-1929 (Box 56, Folder 924)
    - Gregory Pincus, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 925)
    - Max Planck, 1927 (Box 56, Folder 926)
      Visiting professor.
    - Boris Podalsky, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 928)
    - Giovanni Polvani, 1925-1926 (Box 56, Folder 929)
    - Georges Polya, 1924-1925 (Box 56, Folder 930)
    - Maurice Ponte, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 931)
    - Adolf Portmann, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 932)
    - Silvester Prat, 1924-1938 (Box 57, Folder 933)
    - Pedro Prig, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 934)
    - Hem Singh Pruthi, 1925-1929 (Box 57, Folder 935)
    - Franz Raaz, 1927-1931 (Box 57, Folder 936)
    - Isidor Rabi, 1928-1934 (Box 57, Folder 937)
    - Tibor Rado, 1928-1934 (Box 57, Folder 938)
    - George Y. Rainich, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 939)
    - Louis Rapkine, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 940)
    - Franco Rasetti, 1928-1929 (Box 57, Folder 941)
    - Witold Raivita-Witanowski, 1925-1928 (Box 57, Folder 942)
    - Roland Read, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 943)
    - Franklin Regan, 1926-1936 (Box 57, Folder 944)
    - Franklin Regan, 1926-1936 (Box 57, Folder 945)
    - Ettore Remotti, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 946)
    - Edwin Renholm, 1924-1932 (Box 57, Folder 947)
    - Dimitri Riabouchinsky, 1926-1929 (Box 57, Folder 948)
    - William T. Richards, 1923-1934 (Box 57, Folder 949)
    - Oscar Rice, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 950)
    - Oscar Rice, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 951)
    - Alexander Robertson, 1924-1928 (Box 58, Folder 952)
    - Howard P. Robertson, 1925-1929 (Box 58, Folder 953)
    - Robert Roger, 1926-1931 (Box 58, Folder 954)
    - Leon Rosenfeld, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 955)
    - Svein Rosseland, 1924-1929 (Box 58, Folder 956)
    - Olaf Rove, 1924-1929 (Box 58, Folder 957)
    - Georges Ruszckowski, 1924-1934 (Box 58, Folder 958)
    - Edward Saereus, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 959)
    - Peter Saldan, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 960)
    - Jean Savard, 1927-1928 (Box 58, Folder 961)
    - Walter Saxer, 1926-1934 (Box 58, Folder 962)
    - George Scheff, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 963)
    - Willam Scherrer, 1927-1932 (Box 58, Folder 964)
    - Ludwig Scheuring, 1926-1935 (Box 58, Folder 965)
    - Jan Schilt, 1925-1934 (Box 58, Folder 966)
    - Svend Schon, 1926-1927 (Box 58, Folder 967)
    - Oscar Schotte, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 968)
    - Bruno Schussnig, 1926-1929 (Box 58, Folder 969)
    - Boris Schiawanwitsch, 1925-1926 (Box 58, Folder 970)
    - Beniamino Segre, 1926-1931 (Box 58, Folder 971)
    - E. Sidney Semmens, 1925-1926 (Box 58, Folder 972)
    - August Seybold, 1925-1935 (Box 58, Folder 973)
    - Caspar Shapiro, 1928-1930 (Box 58, Folder 974)
    - A. M. Showalter, 1925-1929 (Box 59, Folder 975)
    - Carl Siegel, 1924-1926 (Box 59, Folder 976)
    - Joseph H. Simons, 1928-1929 (Box 59, Folder 977)
    - G. G. Simpson, 1926-1927 (Box 59, Folder 978)
    - Ajrille Sinelnikoff, 1928-1933 (Box 59, Folder 979)
    - Dmitry Skobeltzyn, 1928-1930 (Box 59, Folder 980)
    - Stanislaw Skowron, 1924-1927 (Box 59, Folder 981)
    - Paul Slavenas, 1925-1938 (Box 59, Folder 982)
    - Lyndon Small, 1927-1928 (Box 59, Folder 983)
    - Milutin Smiljanitch, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 984)
    - Stanislaw Snieszko, 1929-1931 (Box 59, Folder 985)
    - Harry Sobotka, 1924-1936 (Box 59, Folder 986)
    - Boris Sokoloff, 1924 (Box 59, Folder 987)
    - Andrew Solton, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 988)
    - Ludwig Sommer, 1926-1934 (Box 59, Folder 989)
    - Piritim Sorokin, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 990)
    - Hans Speman, 1926-1927 (Box 59, Folder 991)
    - Hertha Sponer, 1925-1927 (Box 59, Folder 992)
    - Alfred Stamm, 1927-1928 (Box 59, Folder 993)
    - Henry Stauss, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 994)
    - J. H. Schuwrmans Stekhoven, 1926-1932 (Box 59, Folder 995)
    - Otto Stelling, 1924-1927 (Box 60, Folder 996)
    - Curt Stern, 1924-1927 (Box 60, Folder 997)
    - T. J. B. Stier, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 998)
    - Ivan Stranski, 1926 (Box 60, Folder 999)
    - Martin Straumanis, 1926-1927 (Box 60, Folder 1000)
    - William D. Strong, 1926 (Box 60, Folder 1001)
      Anthropology.
    - D. J. Struik, 1924-1933 (Box 60, Folder 1002)
    - Otto Struve, 1926-1931 (Box 60, Folder 1003)
    - Horace Stunkard, 1924 (Box 60, Folder 1004)
    - Charles Swingle, 1926-1930 (Box 60, Folder 1005)
    - Stephen Szczeniowski, 1927-1934 (Box 60, Folder 1006)
    - Piotr Szymanski, 1928-1929 (Box 60, Folder 1007)
    - Miroslav Tamele, 1924-1930 (Box 60, Folder 1008)
      Electrochemistry.
    - James Taylor, 1925-1932 (Box 60, Folder 1009)
    - John B. Taylor, 1927-1932 (Box 60, Folder 1010)
    - Curt Teichert, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 1011)
    - Joseph M. Thomas, 1926-1930 (Box 60, Folder 1012)
    - Tracy Thomas, 1924-1926 (Box 60, Folder 1013)
    - Lars Thomassen, 1924-1930 (Box 60, Folder 1014)
    - Gerhard Thomsen, 1926-1932 (Box 60, Folder 1015)
    - Sylva Thurlow, 1924-1925 (Box 60, Folder 1016)
    - Georges Tiercy, 1927-1928 (Box 61, Folder 1017)
    - Constantin Toumanoff, 1926-1927 (Box 61, Folder 1018)
    - Mildred Trotter, 1925-1926 (Box 61, Folder 1019)
    - Donald Townend, 1924-1932 (Box 61, Folder 1020)
    - Bjorn Trumpy, 1928-1931 (Box 61, Folder 1021)
    - Vladimir Ulehla, 1924-1937 (Box 61, Folder 1022)
    - Franz Ulrich, 1924-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1023)
    - Albrecht Unsold, 1927-1933 (Box 61, Folder 1024)
    - Miroslav Valouch, 1925-1934 (Box 61, Folder 1025)
    - Robert Van De Graaff, 1928-1933 (Box 61, Folder 1026)
    - Bartel Van Der Waerden, 1925-1933 (Box 61, Folder 1027)
    - Florin Vasilesco, 1927-1931 (Box 61, Folder 1028)
    - Emilie Vejnarova, 1926 (Box 61, Folder 1029)
    - Leopold Vietoris, 1924-1934 (Box 61, Folder 1030)
    - H. B. Vincent, 1927 (Box 61, Folder 1031)
    - Arthur von Hippel, 1927-1928 (Box 61, Folder 1032)
    - Vivian Voss, 1926-1928 (Box 61, Folder 1033)
    - George Vranceanu, 1927-1934 (Box 61, Folder 1034)
    - Nicolas Wagner, 1927-1928 (Box 61, Folder 1035)
      Plant cytology.
    - Frederick Walker, 1924-1925 (Box 61, Folder 1036)
      Petrology.
    - Oswald J. Walker, 1926-1938 (Box 61, Folder 1038)
    - Joseph L. Walsh, 1925-1927 (Box 61, Folder 1039)
    - Heinrich Walter, 1929-1932 (Box 61, Folder 1040)
    - Oswald Alwin Walther, 1926-1930 (Box 61, Folder 1041)
    - Alan T. Waterman, 1927-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1042)
    - David L. Watson, 1925-1932 (Box 62, Folder 1043)
    - Thomas J. Webb, 1925-1931 (Box 62, Folder 1044)
    - Max Wahrli, 1924-1925 (Box 62, Folder 1045)
    - Andrew Weil, 1926-1933 (Box 62, Folder 1046)
    - Robert Weill, 1926-1929 (Box 62, Folder 1047)
    - Alexander Weinstein, 1924-1925 (Box 62, Folder 1048)
    - Alexander Weinstein, 1925-1936 (Box 62, Folder 1049)
    - Ernst Weiss, 1928 (Box 62, Folder 1050)
    - Paul Weiss, 1927-1928 (Box 62, Folder 1051)
    - Jules Weissfeiler, 1925-1930 (Box 62, Folder 1052)
    - Otto Werner, 1928-1929 (Box 62, Folder 1053)
    - Ludwig Wertenstein, 1925-1934 (Box 62, Folder 1054)
    - George Wetzler, 1925 (Box 62, Folder 1055)
    - Harvey White, 1929-1930 (Box 62, Folder 1056)
    - Lancelot Whyte, 1928-1931 (Box 62, Folder 1057)
    - John W. Williams, 1927 (Box 62, Folder 1058)
    - Wilfred Wilson, 1925-1929 (Box 62, Folder 1059)
    - John G. Winans, 1928-1929 (Box 62, Folder 1060)
    - Aurel Winter, 1929 (Box 62, Folder 1061)
    - Oskar Wintersteiner, 1926-1927 (Box 62, Folder 1062)
    - Emos Witmer, 1927-1928 (Box 62, Folder 1063)
    - Emil Witschi, 1925-1929 (Box 62, Folder 1064)
    - Carl Wohrman, 1927-1928 (Box 62, Folder 1065)
    - Ernst Wolf, 1925-1931 (Box 63, Folder 1066)
    - Lawrence Wolfrom, 1927-1933 (Box 63, Folder 1067)
    - Erwin Wrede, 1928 (Box 63, Folder 1068)
    - Winthrop Wright, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 1069)
    - John Wulff, 1929 (Box 63, Folder 1070)
    - Rene Wurmser, 1924-1926 (Box 63, Folder 1071)
    - William Wynne-Jones, 1927-1933 (Box 63, Folder 1072)
    - Dan M. Yost, 1928-1932 (Box 63, Folder 1073)
    - D. Yovanovitch, 1924-1926 (Box 63, Folder 1074)
    - Paul T. Youny, 1926-1934 (Box 63, Folder 1075)
    - Frederick Zachariasen, 1927-1934 (Box 63, Folder 1076)
    - Herman Zanstra, 1923-1937 (Box 63, Folder 1077)
    - Oscar Zarischi, 1924-1926 (Box 63, Folder 1078)
    - Johannes Zernike, 1924-1929 (Box 63, Folder 1079)
    - Fritz Zwicky, 1924-1933 (Box 63, Folder 1080)
    - Antoni Zygmund, 1929-1931 (Box 63, Folder 1081)
    - Fellowships in Science - Far East, 1925-1927 (Box 63, Folder 1082)
    - Frank P. Bowden, 1926-1934 (Box 63, Folder 1083)
    - Cecil E. Eddy, 1926-1928 (Box 63, Folder 1084)
    - Yusuki Hagihara, 1928-1933 (Box 63, Folder 1085)
    - Tetsuo Inukai, 1925-1928 (Box 63, Folder 1086)
    - Masashi Ishikawa, 1926-1928 (Box 64, Folder 1087)
    - Eisaker Kawaguchi, 1925-1928 (Box 64, Folder 1088)
      Seriology.
    - Neil B. Lewis, 1926-1928 (Box 64, Folder 1089)
    - Leslie H. Martin, 1926-1927 (Box 64, Folder 1090)
    - Carey D. Miller, 1926-1927 (Box 64, Folder 1091)
    - Shichiroku Nomura, 1925-1934 (Box 64, Folder 1092)
      Animal physiology.
    - Diazo Nukujama, 1925-1927 (Box 64, Folder 1093)
    - Yudzuru Ogura, 1925-1926 (Box 64, Folder 1094)
    - J. Robert Oppenheimer, 1926-1945 (Box 64, Folder 1095)
    - Stuart Pennycuick, 1927-1934 (Box 64, Folder 1096)
    - Sukeaki Saki, 1925-1927 (Box 64, Folder 1097)
    - Osamu Shinoda, 1925-1928 (Box 64, Folder 1098)
    - Harusada Suginome, 1925-1932 (Box 64, Folder 1099)
    - Oscar Tiegs, 1926-1931 (Box 64, Folder 1100)
    - Chiao Tsai, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 1101)
    - A. B. Walkom, 1926-1936 (Box 64, Folder 1102)
  - Fellowships in Agriculture, 4
    This subseries consists of fellowship files in agriculture. Fellowships in the Far East are listed at the end of the subseries.
    Arrangement
    Persistent ID ref2471 (Box 72/Folder 1210) deleted because not used.
    - Fellowships in Agriculture - General Policy, 1924-June 1925 (Box 64, Folder 1103)
    - Fellowships in Agriculture - General Policy, August 1925-1928 (Box 65, Folder 1104)
    - Fellowships in Agriculture - General Policy, August 1925-1928 (Box 65, Folder 1105)
    - Fellowships in Agriculture - General Policy, August 1925-1928 (Box 65, Folder 1106)
    - Fellowships in Agriculture - General Policy, August 1925-1928 (Box 65, Folder 1107)
    - Donald B. Anderson, 1926-1929 (Box 65, Folder 1108)
    - J. A. Anderson, 1925-1935 (Box 65, Folder 1109)
    - Alexander Arany, 1924-1934 (Box 65, Folder 1110)
      Soil science.
    - Sydney Asdell, 1926-1936 (Box 65, Folder 1111)
    - Johan Aslander, 1925-1933 (Box 65, Folder 1112)
    - Vaino Auer, 1925-1927 (Box 65, Folder 1113)
    - Tonnes Bacher, 1927-1929 (Box 66, Folder 1114)
    - Walter Baggli, 1925-1926 (Box 66, Folder 1115)
    - Otto Benderki, 1925-1929 (Box 66, Folder 1116)
      Veterinary medicine.
    - Franz Benesch, 1926 (Box 66, Folder 1117)
    - Jan Bijhouwer, 1926-1949 (Box 66, Folder 1118)
    - Raymond R. Birch, 1925-1927 (Box 66, Folder 1119)
    - Gyula Biro, 1924-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1120)
    - Jakob H. Blom, 1926-1935 (Box 66, Folder 1121)
    - Rudolf Bokor, 1926-1930 (Box 66, Folder 1122)
      Agricultural chemistry.
    - Paul Borgedahl, 1926-1927 (Box 66, Folder 1123)
    - Avice Borohyer, 1926 (Box 66, Folder 1124)
    - Andrew Cairns, 1924-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1125)
    - Gladys Cameron, 1926-1928 (Box 66, Folder 1126)
    - Sidney Cameron, 1928-1930 (Box 66, Folder 1127)
    - Albert Carlstrom, 1926-1928 (Box 66, Folder 1128)
    - Dwight C. Carpenter, 1927-1935 (Box 67, Folder 1129)
      Protein chemistry.
    - Enid Cauty, 1924-1931 (Box 67, Folder 1130)
      Home economics and rural extension.
    - Helene Chenot, 1924-1925 (Box 67, Folder 1131)
      Culinary economics.
    - Marin Chiritescu-Arva, 1926-1930 (Box 67, Folder 1132)
      Soil biology.
    - Ferdinard Chodat, 1924-1934 (Box 67, Folder 1133)
      Plant geography.
    - Ulla Christensen, 1924-1931 (Box 67, Folder 1134)
      Club work.
    - Michail Christoff, 1925-1936 (Box 67, Folder 1135)
    - Jens C. Clausen, 1926-1933 (Box 67, Folder 1136)
    - Roy E. Clausen, 1925-1926 (Box 67, Folder 1137)
    - George Conant, 1924 (Box 67, Folder 1138)
    - George Constantinescu, 1925-1927 (Box 67, Folder 1139)
    - Caspar Coolhaas, 1928 (Box 67, Folder 1140)
    - Luis Crespi, 1924 (Box 67, Folder 1141)
    - Norman Cunliffe, 1926-1927 (Box 67, Folder 1142)
    - Carl Danelius, 1925-1927 (Box 68, Folder 1143)
      Animal pathology.
    - Egons Darzins, 1925-1927 (Box 68, Folder 1144)
      Agricultural bacteriology.
    - D. Delgado De Torres, 1924-1939 (Box 68, Folder 1145)
    - Karl Demeter, 1924-1927 (Box 68, Folder 1146)
      Dairy bacteriology.
    - Dezso Deseo, 1924-1930 (Box 68, Folder 1147)
      Animal nutrition.
    - Miklos De Siegescu, 1924-1928 (Box 68, Folder 1148)
    - Miklos De Siegescu - Report (Box 68, Folder 1149)
    - Sophie Detaille, 1924-1925 (Box 68, Folder 1150)
    - Louis D'Hauteserve, 1926-1927 (Box 68, Folder 1151)
    - Minko Dobreff, 1925-1926 (Box 69, Folder 1152)
      Cell stimulation.